[
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 67? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "14095.46",
      "options": [
        "14093.96",
        "14096.96",
        "14098.46",
        "14095.46"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 97? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "29544.26",
      "options": [
        "29544.26",
        "29542.76",
        "29547.26",
        "29545.76"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 23? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "1661.06",
      "options": [
        "1662.56",
        "1659.56",
        "1664.06",
        "1661.06"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 14? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "615.44",
      "options": [
        "615.44",
        "613.94",
        "616.94",
        "618.44"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 11? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "379.94",
      "options": [
        "381.44",
        "378.44",
        "379.94",
        "382.94"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 53? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "8820.26",
      "options": [
        "8820.26",
        "8823.26",
        "8818.76",
        "8821.76"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 72? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "16277.76",
      "options": [
        "16277.76",
        "16279.26",
        "16276.26",
        "16280.76"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 1? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "3.14",
      "options": [
        "6.14",
        "4.64",
        "1.64",
        "3.14"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 67? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "14095.46",
      "options": [
        "14098.46",
        "14096.96",
        "14093.96",
        "14095.46"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the area of a circle <br> with radius 47? (Use \u03c0 \u2248 3.14)",
      "correctAnswer": "6936.26",
      "options": [
        "6934.76",
        "6936.26",
        "6939.26",
        "6937.76"
      ]
    }
]